{
    "id": "e44f84ce6d51450db67b1f2fcf353230",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Pass",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Could you pass this brochure ....................................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "around",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7ffd2b0a63d64db0a6973da81a2ec099"
        },
        {
            "question": "My grandmother passed .................................... last year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "away",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4c2423c69947485b9ac4c277a4daf207"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the boy who just passed ..................................... the window?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "by",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "22aa07dbc2204bde959daa56f891403a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He tried to pass it ........................................ as an original painting but the curator could easily tell it was fake.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e3aad73ae3554aa7b2947abe81665503"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have got a good job offer and I just don’t want to pass it .......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "on",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ce696ddc51db4d56a8e2cf8aa00d916a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She passed ........................................ at the ripe old age of ninety.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "on",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "526db6c2bdf6489fadf91224335d4a09"
        },
        {
            "question": "All that belongs to him will pass ....................................... his son when he dies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "on",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f67a1d70df094edcbe27cd95728416f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I’m sorry but I think I will have to pass ................................... our invitation.",
            "description": "Pass up and pass on are both possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "on",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "80026abfdf0f423282aefbf127d06507"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was furious with the management because they passed him ...................................... in favor of a younger person.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "over",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6f3e705c7eb14da1b67d5b2867ba14e2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I passed ..................................... Mangalore on my way to Calicut.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "across",
                "over",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0d6193753c914ee48545ffc897b7a4f5"
        }
    ]
}